请看听力部分第一节。
of small after B, next
第一节，听下面五段对话，
每段对话后有一个小题，
从题中所给的
三个选项。
当中选出最佳选项。
听完每段对话后，你都有十秒钟的时间来回答有关小题和阅读下一小题。
每段对话仅读一遍。
现在，你有五秒钟的时间
阅读第一小题的有关内容。
How was school today,
Great! I got an A on my exam, a B on essay writing, and our teacher said we'd go
camping tomorrow. Hello, Olivia.
Haven't seen you for some time.
What are you reading?
Just checking the job page of the local newspaper.
I've found that many people like to study English on the Internet.
How about you?
Well, as a of fact, I've just started taking some courses.
It is a good way to improve English.
I heard that some airlines had changed their flight restrictions, and I need to find
out what they are.
There are websites that list the general restrictions.
You may have a look there.
Jason, how long have you been with this company?
Five months this week.
I would say that's enough time to learn that we have rules here.
Why didn't you report before you made the decision?
第一节到此结束。
第二节，听下面。
练五段对话或独白。
每段对话或独白后有几个小题，
从题中所给的
三个选项中选出最佳选项。
听每段对话或独白前。
你将有时间阅读各个小题，
每小题五秒钟。
听完后，各小题将给出五秒钟的作答时间。
每段对话或独白读两遍
听下面一段对话，回答第六和第七两个小题。
现在你有十秒钟的时间
阅读这两个小题。
How about driving to the beach this weekend?
There are too many people there.
I prefer a picnic in the woods or by the lake.
Then let's go to the lake.
It's just an hour's drive from here.
We can bike around the lake and swim after the picnic lunch.
You're always so sporty.
Bring your bike if you like, but I will bring a good book with me.
How about driving to the beach this weekend?
There are too many people there.
I prefer a picnic in the woods or by the lake.
Then let's go to the lake.
It's just an hour's drive from here.
We can bike around the lake and swim after the picnic lunch.
You're always so sporty.
Bring your bike if you like, but I will bring a good book with me.
听下面一段对话，回答第八和第九两个小题。
现在。你有十秒钟的时间
阅读这两个小题。
Mr. Smith, I was wondering if I could change my major from biology to political
science or psychology.
Which year are you in?
Second term, year two.
Okay, but these majors are very different.
You probably will have to take more classes and prepare for more exams, and you
would be graduating a year later.
Oh no, I hate graduating later than all my friends.
I'd better stick to my present major then.
Mr. Smith, I was wondering if I could change my major from biology to political
science or psychology.
Which year are you in?
Second term, year two.
Okay, but these majors are very different.
You probably will have to take more classes and prepare for more exams, and you
would be graduating a year later.
Oh no, I hate graduating later than all my friends.
I'd better stick to my present major then.
听下面一段对话，回答第十。
至第十二三个小题。
现在你有十五秒钟的时间
阅读这三个小题。
Hey Mark, I'm putting you on a new project.
You'll have to go to California.
What should I do there?
You have to collect and review the sales data from all the branch stores.
If you find something missing, work with their sales managers to get the information
you need to complete the analysis.
Sounds like a of work.
It's a pretty big project, so take someone with you.
I think you can finish in a week if the two of you are working on it.
When should we start off?
You needn't hurry so much.
I'll give you two days for preparations and packing up.
Who should I get in touch with when I get there?
Lisa, I'll email you the necessary information.
Who do you suggest should go with me?
Either Jack or Peter.
Let's say Peter.
He's just finished his project, and he is more experienced.
Great. Keep me updated.
Hey Mark, I'm putting you on a new project.
You'll have to go to California.
What should I do there?
You have to collect and review the sales data from all the branch stores.
If you find something missing, work with their sales managers to get the information
you need to complete the analysis.
Sounds like a lot of work.
It's a pretty big project, so take someone with you.
I think you can finish in a week if the two of you are working on it.
When should we start off?
You needn't hurry so much.
I'll give you two days for preparations and packing up.
Who should I get in touch with when I get there?
Lisa, I'll email you the necessary information.
Who do you suggest should go with me?
Either Jack or Peter.
Let's say Peter.
He's just finished his project, and he is more experienced.
Great. Keep me updated.
听下面一段对话，回答第十三至第十六
四个小题。
现在你有二十秒钟的时间。
边阅读这四个小题。
Thank you. Good evening.
Welcome to Around the Globe with Susan Davidson.
Our guest today is Charlie Hamilton, a photographer who spent a month and a half in
the Amazon. He's going to share with us the challenges and responsibilities of his
work. Charlie, the Amazon people have rarely seen people from outside, and you look
so different. How do you approach them?
That's true, but if you spend enough time, you get to know them.
Actually, we can laugh about the same things even if we can't talk.
One of your pictures I really like shows the villagers and you together by a river,
laughing. There seemed no barrier at all.
Indeed. That was only a couple of days after I went there, but everyone was just
relaxed with me.
We're all having fun.
In fact, what I like most is everyone's laughing.
Nowadays, we tend to show the unhappy side of people's life in the Amazon.
The trees are being cut down, and these people are sad.
But what I want to show is they still have fun.
That's a really special point of view.
Thank you for letting us get closer to our fellow beings around the
Good evening. Welcome to Around the Globe with Susan Davidson.
Our guest today is Charlie Hamilton,
a photographer who spent a month and a half in the Amazon.
He's going to share with us the challenges and responsibilities of his work.
Charlie, the Amazon people have rarely seen people from outside, and you look so
different. How do you approach them?
That's true. But if you spend enough time, you get to know them.
Actually, we can laugh about the same things even if we can't talk.
One of your pictures I really like shows the villagers and you together by a river,
laughing. There seemed no barrier at all.
Indeed. That was only a couple of days after I went there, but everyone was just
relaxed with me.
We're all having fun.
In fact, what I like most is everyone's laughing.
Nowadays, we tend to show the unhappy side of people's life in the Amazon.
The trees are being cut down, and these people are sad.
But what I want to show is they still have fun.
That's a really special point of view.
Thank you for letting us get closer to our fellow beings around the
听下面一段独白，回答第十七。
至第二十四个小题。
现在你有二十秒钟的时间
阅读这四个小题。
Hi, everyone. It is raining now.
We have to give up our plans for a boat trip along the River Thames and a walk along
the South Bank.
But the good news is we still have a huge selection of world -class museums, and
many of them are free for visitors.
You know, the UK's capital isn't a bad place to spend a rainy day.
So our rainy tour of London's museums today starts in the Science and National
History Museums of West London and finishes at the National Gallery.
We'll start our museum tour in the heart of London, South Kensington.
South Kensington is well known for its old buildings, fantastic restaurants, and
many designer shops.
But the real reason visitors flood here is for the chance to experience three of the
city's best museums.
Victoria and Albert Museum,
the National History Museum, and the Science Museum.
All of them happen to be within walking distance from one another, so you won't get
wet. Today, happens to be the last Thursday of the month, so we can enjoy free
guided tours, talks, and events at the National History Museum.
Remember, we have to leave there at 1pm.
Finally, we'll arrive at the National Gallery.
It's an 1800s building, home to over 2,000 works of art by famous painters like
Leonardo da Vinci, Claude Monet, and Vincent van Gogh.
Hi everyone. It is raining now.
We have to give up our plans for a boat trip along the River Thames and a walk along
the South Bank.
But the good news is we still have a huge selection of world -class museums, and
many of them are free for visitors.
You know, the UK's capital isn't a bad place to spend a rainy day.
So our rainy tour of London's museums today starts in the Science and National
History Museums of West London and finishes at the National Gallery.
We'll start our museum tour in the heart of London, South Kensington.
South Kensington is well known for its old buildings, fantastic restaurants, and
many designer shops.
But the real reason visitors flood here is for the chance to experience three of the
city's best museums, Victoria and Albert Museum,
the National History Museum, and the Science Museum.
All of them happen to be within walking distance from one another, so you won't get
wet. Today it happens to be the last Thursday of the month, so we can enjoy free
guided tours, talks, and events at the National History Museum.
Remember, we have to leave there at 1pm.
Finally, we'll arrive at the National Gallery.
It's an 1800s building, home to over 2,000 works of art by famous painters like
Leonardo da Vinci,
Claude Monet, and Vincent van Gogh.
第二节到此结束。
现在你有两分钟的时间，将试卷上的答案
转涂到答题卡上。
Thank you for watching.
Thank you. Thank you.
The second
听力部分第二次考试到。
此結束。